This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Lucky D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
The Navy triumphed in the War of the Best,
and Luffy, unable to save his brother Ace, fell into despair.
But this is a story from ten years ago in the East Bloomer.
What the hell did you do?!
Ace, no!
Don't do it!
Where can freedom be found?
A sad departure of a boy!
Where did you start?
A awake, Cortese.
Question 2,
Thanks, but what are you guys doing here?
We are too late, are we?
Yikes. You got roughed up pretty bad, Luffy.
You okay?
I'll make it.
And what about Sabo? I don't see him.
He's safe in Hightown. He isn't with us anymore.
Easy now.
I know you. You're that bandit gorilla from Mount Corvo.
Bandit, yes. Gorilla, no.
But that's not the point here.
The point is, like it or not, these kids are my responsibility.
Even if I felt like killing the brats myself, that doesn't mean you get to.
Now, I'll say it again. Nobody hurts my boys.
So I'll let you walk away.
But if you don't, I guarantee you're gonna be sorry.
I got nothing to lose.
All right, then. Let's dance.
Now! Everybody run!
Hurry up! What are you doing?
Ace, we gotta get going.
What's the matter?
I'm staying.
I won't run.
You've got nothing to gain here, you little idiot!
Look! This place is on fire!
Also, Blue Gem is a hardened criminal.
A little kid like you shouldn't be fighting him to the death!
I...I gotta help Ace!
Cut it out!
Damn it!
Take Luffy.
And get your butts back to the hideout.
What about you?
I'll take care of Ace.
No matter how many asses I gotta kick.
You're so cool!
Now come!
Yes ma'am!
Ace!
Come home safe boss!
We'll be waiting for you!
Look at that.
How brave.
But at the end of the day, you're just a woman and a child against a pirate.
Do you like those odds?
Only two kinds of people survive in battle.
The strong and the cowardly.
Bravery doesn't enter the picture, I'm afraid.
Oh, is that so?
Hmm.
Have it your way.
Take that!
We're all dead!
Look around you!
There's no way out now!
Everything was fine!
How could this happen so quickly?
I'm burning!
You and everyone else!
Just let me die already!
Oh技 liXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX Sem 098 10xXXXX ile eccXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX imm050XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX affected aufg0XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX xXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX
through the fire whoa did somebody do that on purpose who cares now we can get out of this
hellhole hey look you guys there's a ship here it's waiting down by the shore i don't know who
and i don't know how but i think they're here to save us let's go hurry before the fire comes back
i've seen nobles do some dreadful things but this takes the cake absolutely reprehensible
anywho this locale is rather out of the way how did you hear the news were you keeping an eye on
this country or perhaps is there something here of interest to you what's happening here will happen
in the rest of the world soon enough human beings can't be thrown away a world that allows that must
change no matter how long it takes i will stop out this misery and injustice i can't stay here because
if i do then i'll never be free the children born in this country must have a future that they can
believe in
if it's freedom you want so long as you have the will to fight for it
you are welcome aboard this ship
did they find sabo yet i called in the military for help they'll find him soon enough
all we can do now is wait i see he does like to give us a hard time that he does
are you sure that wall will protect us it seems like the fire could spread here any second
it won't last long surely they'll lead us into high town until it passes
not a chance those gates are so tight even a flea can't get through
no matter how their friends cried ace and adan did not emerge from the flames consuming gray terminal
easy kiddo you're still hurt what are you doing what do you think i'm looking for ace and adan
that's not gonna work see told you you'll just make things worse
i'm worried too but for right now we just have to wait the military is down in gray terminal word is
they were sent in to clean up everything after the fire died down and by clean up i mean take care of
any remaining evidence i'm sure that extends to killing off the survivors too you'll be no exception
i can't just leave him out there and we have to let zappo know that we didn't die
hell of a view don't you think hell of a mess we have to clean up nothing to laugh about that's for sure
that's what we're going to do
orders say to shoot any survivors we find on site yeah what survivors it's weird though i've hardly
seen any corpses that fire was pretty intense probably burned up their bones too
i was up all night scared that fire would get over the wall should have known they wouldn't burn decent
people like us i heard blue jam's ship wasn't quite so lucky good let's hope the bastard was on it when it
burned
it's morning
why good morning what a beautiful day yes i dare say it's even more lovely than yesterday
it's been a long night what do you say you give up the hide and seek
questions
uh
can't you see it will always end this way saboe the police and military have photos of you
This way, Sabo.
The police and military have photos of you.
Try all you want.
There's no escape.
You'll never get out of Hightown, let alone this house,
unless I expressly permit it.
I need you on guard duty.
Now, I'll look into getting you new uniforms.
I'm sorry, sir, but we have other duties.
I'm a nobleman.
That means I get what I want.
Don't worry, I'll have a word with your superiors.
Yes, sir.
Listen, Sabo, it's not too late for you.
From now on, you'll lock yourself in your room
and learn to be a proper noble.
No!
I don't want to be cruel,
but I am certainly capable of it
and anything else I so desire.
You could disappear, just like your friends.
Are we clear?
I think so.
Ace, Luffy...
If Stella can study hard, then so can you.
Everything will work out fine.
And then your parents,
who work so hard to build a proper future for you,
can finally be happy.
Won't that be nice?
I'm sure it'll be nice for you as well.
Just give it some time.
Papa!
If you're sad, I can help.
Dependable as always, Stella.
We've got that big ceremony coming up, you know.
Let's buy you some new clothes.
You'll look so handsome for the celestial dragon.
There's nothing I can do.
I'm helpless.
All right.
That should do it for today's lesson.
Study hard, and I'll check your homework tomorrow.
Have a pleasant afternoon.
Don't worry, guys.
I'm fine.
And you're tough.
So I know you're okay, too.
There's no way you died in that fire.
I just wish I could see you, even once.
But if people follow me,
they'll find out you're still alive
and you'll be in danger again.
It looks nice from the outside,
but this house is a birdcage.
I'm going to lose my mind
if I have to stay in this stuffy, stuck-up place.
I thought I found freedom,
but it seems to keep slipping away.
Hey, your shift is over.
Oh, yeah?
I lost track of time.
That's because you were sleeping.
No kidding.
By the way, how are things going in town?
The big ceremony is tomorrow, isn't it?
Yeah, and it's wild out there.
Everyone's worked up.
Well, that sucks for me.
A once-in-a-lifetime chance,
and I'm stuck in here.
They have me working all day
while they go to the ceremony.
Nobody else is going to be in the house,
so I got to watch the kid
to make sure he doesn't bail.
A world noble.
I've never seen one.
I wouldn't say it's all bad, buddy.
I mean, just think.
The harbor will be a mess.
The whole town's going to be there.
That's a lot of people to keep track of.
And you only have this one.
That's easy-peasy.
If that's how you feel,
why don't we trade places?
Ha, ha, ha.
Yeah, you wish.
All right, we're off.
Take good care of Sabo.
We won't be back until late.
Yes, sir.
As you wish.
After much anticipation,
the day of the world nobles' visit
to the Goa kingdom arrives at last.
A lavish ceremony is prepared
to greet his ship as it enters the harbor.
Hello, this is Team A on the coast.
The Celestial Dragon ship
is pulling in as we speak.
It should arrive at your location
in a few minutes.
Understood, sir.
Everything looks good.
We'll keep an eye out
for anything strange, though.
Click.
Oh, hey, wait.
Is that a ship leaving port?
A what?
A fishing boat?
Hey, come back!
You're blocking their path!
Why, it's just a child.
A little boy is steering that boat.
Then he's a noble?
But surely all the families are here watching.
It can't be.
No, it can't!
Sabo, he's still at home.
I gave the guard strict orders.
Nice weather today.
It's just perfect for setting sail.
Oh, crap!
That's mine!
It was stolen!
I have nothing to do with this mess!
His flag!
He's got a Jolly Roger on him.
Is he trying to be a pirate or something?
Does it matter?
The kid's flag isn't the issue here.
He's heading straight for the ship.
The Celestial Dragon isn't gonna like this.
Either you lose that boat or you lose your job!
Do you hear me?
Fix it now!
Uh, yes, sir.
Hey!
Get back here, kid!
Are you nuts?
I'm not afraid of anything as long as I'm free.
I just have to be far away from here.
I have to follow my own dream.
Nobody's gonna change me.
Give them a warm welcome, everyone!
Oh, wow, that's one big ship.
It could run right over me easy.
Heh, let's avoid that, shall we?
Uh, uh, he's moving!
That almost got pretty ugly.
What is this display?
Are the commoners attempting to welcome us?
Yes, sir.
Huh?
This is a first for me!
The Celestial Dragons hardly ever make visits like this!
I hope nobody mucks this up!
We didn't burn all those people for nothing!
By the way, what is that wretched little thing?
Hmph.
It seems to be a fishing boat, sir.
That's so cool!
I hope I'm the captain of a big ship like that some day!
It's time to learn your place!
Insolent fool!
What's going on?
He just opened fire!
Ace and Dadan return to their hideout safely after their battle with Blue Jam.
However, the Mountain Bandits scarcely have time to celebrate before the news of Sabo's tragedy reaches their ears.
Luffy despairs, Ace vows revenge, but a letter from Sabo changes their perspective.
On the next, Wood Piece, take good care of him!
A letter from the brother!
I will be king of the pirates!